const langlist = [
    { id: 0, name: 'device language', trans: 'English' },
    { id: 1, name: 'Hindi', trans: 'हिंदी' },
    { id: 2, name: 'Marati', trans: 'मराटी' },
    { id: 3, name: 'Gujarati', trans: 'ગુજરાતી' },
    { id: 4, name: 'Tamil', trans: 'தமிழ்' },
    { id: 5, name: 'Bengali', trans: 'বাংলা' },
    { id: 6, name: 'Telugu', trans: 'తెలుగు' },
    { id: 7, name: 'Kannada', trans: 'ಕನ್ನಡ' },
    { id: 8, name: 'Malayalam', trans: 'മലയാളം' },
    { id: 9, name: 'French', trans: 'Française' },
    { id: 10, name: 'Nepali', trans: 'नेपाली' },
    { id: 11, name: 'Russian', trans: 'Русский' }
];

const questions = [
    { id: 0, question: 'About end-to-end encryption', },
    { id: 1, question: 'Seeing "Waiting for this message. This may take a...', },
    { id: 2, question: 'Get Started', },
    { id: 3, question: 'About view once', },
    { id: 4, question: 'About disappearing messages', },
    { id: 5, question: 'How to turn on chat lock', },
    { id: 6, question: 'How to register your phone number', },
    { id: 7, question: 'Received verification code without requesting it', },
    { id: 8, question: 'About unofficial apps', },
    { id: 9, question: 'About linked devices', }
];

const contacts = [
    { id: 0, name: 'Jesiliya', phone: '6382259675', location: 'Tamil Nadu, India', email: 'jesiliya@yopmail.com', password: '123456' },
    { id: 1, name: 'Priya', phone: '9150177954', location: 'Tamil Nadu, India', email: 'priya@yopmail.com', password: '123456' },
    { id: 2, name: 'Iswarya', phone: '8870891444', location: 'Tamil Nadu, India', email: 'iswarya@yopmail.com', password: '123456' },
    { id: 3, name: 'Mohana', phone: '8754396128', location: 'Tamil Nadu, India', email: 'mohana@yopmail.com', password: '123456' },
    { id: 4, name: 'Sandhiya', phone: '6381144270', location: 'Tamil Nadu, India', email: 'sandhiya@yopmail.com', password: '123456' },
    { id: 5, name: 'Abubakkar', phone: '9597472614', location: 'Tamil Nadu, India', email: 'abubakkar@yopmail.com', password: '123456' },
];

export { langlist, questions, contacts }